http://www.advantagecap.com/privacy-policy

Privacy PolicyYour privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.We will not share personal information with third parties.We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. Our PortfolioHow We InvestEquityDebtSmall BusinessAgribusinessSolarAffordable HousingHow We InvestVisionTeamNewsWe're with you. Small business resources during COVID-19.Learn MoreOur PortfolioHow We InvestEquityDebtSmall BusinessAgribusinessSolarAffordable HousingVisionTeamNewsOur OfficesAustin900 South Capital of Texas HwyLas Cimas Building 4, Suite 480Austin,TX78746512-380-1168Get DirectionsMeet the TeamCalifornia6293 Silverado TrailNapa,CA94558707.944.2310Get DirectionsMeet the TeamHanover, NH3 Lebanon StreetHanover,NH03755603.676.7160Get DirectionsMeet the TeamHartford, CTc/o Ironwood Capital45 Nod RoadAvon,CT06001860.409.2100Get DirectionsMeet the TeamHuntsville, AL207 East Side Square, Suite 200Huntsville,AL35801256.883.8711Get DirectionsMeet the TeamJackson, MS208 West Georgetown StreetCrystal Springs,MS39059601.954.6636Get DirectionsMeet the TeamLas Vegas9205 W. Russell Road. Suite 240Las Vegas,NV89148702-793-4342Get DirectionsMeet the TeamNew Orleans909 Poydras Street, Suite 2230New Orleans,LA70112504.522.4850Get DirectionsMeet the TeamNew York156 West 56th Street, Suite 801New York,NY10019646.685.8755Get DirectionsMeet the TeamRenoReno,NV89433775.409.3266Get DirectionsMeet the TeamSt. Louis7733 Forsyth Blvd., Suite 1400St. Louis,MO63105314.725.0800Get DirectionsMeet the TeamWashington, D.C.1028 33rd Street NWSuite 200Washington,DC20007202.337.1661Get DirectionsMeet the TeamFollow UsLinkedInFacebookTwitterLinksPortfolioHow We InvestVisionTeamNewsContact PressTerms of UsePrivacy PolicySt. Louis7733 Forsyth Blvd. Suite 1400St. Louis, MO 63105Phone: (314) 725-0800New Orleans909 Poydras Street, Suite 2230New Orleans, LA 70112Phone: (504) 522-4850New Orleans909 Poydras Street, Suite 2230New Orleans, LA 70112Phone: (504) 522-4850Advantage Capital Funds ®Our Capital - Your Advantage ®Advantage Capital is an investment adviser registered under the Investment Advisers Act of 1940.  Registration does not imply a certain level of skill or training.  The information on this website is not intended to be an advertisement concerning investment advisory services or an offer to sell, or a solicitation of an offer to purchase an interest in any security.  Advantage Capital is an equal opportunity provider.  Any reference to third parties on this website is not intended to imply that these entities are endorsing Advantage Capital, nor is Advantage Capital making a representation or warranty as to the level of satisfaction regarding any prior or existing relationship that a third party has had with Advantage Capital.Contact PressTerms of UsePrivacy Policy© Advantage Capital 2020.   Built by Skyrocket
